export const mockQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      'Often called the Red Planet due to its distinctive color, which planet in our solar system has been the focus of countless missions and is believed to have once had liquid water on its surface?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Venus',
      B: 'Mars',
      C: 'Jupiter',
      D: 'Saturn',
    },
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question:
      'In what year did the RMS Titanic famously sink after striking an iceberg during its maiden voyage across the Atlantic Ocean, leading to one of history’s most tragic maritime disasters?',
    choices: {
      A: '1912',
      B: '1921',
      C: '1905',
      D: '1898',
    },
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Despite being one of the most influential musicians in history, which reggae icon never achieved a Number 1 hit on the U.S. Billboard Hot 100 chart?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Elvis Presley',
      B: 'The Beatles',
      C: 'Beyoncé',
      D: 'Bob Marley',
    },
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Although flatbreads have existed for thousands of years in many cultures, modern pizza as we know it—with sauce and cheese—originated in which country?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Italy',
      B: 'France',
      C: 'Spain',
      D: 'Greece',
    },
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which element, crucial for breathing and life on Earth, is represented by the symbol 'O' on the periodic table?",
    choices: {
      A: 'Gold',
      B: 'Osmium',
      C: 'Oxygen',
      D: 'Zinc',
    },
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Covering more surface area than any other ocean and home to the Mariana Trench, which ocean lies between Asia, Australia, and the Americas?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Atlantic Ocean',
      B: 'Arctic Ocean',
      C: 'Indian Ocean',
      D: 'Pacific Ocean',
    },
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which British author wrote the dystopian novel '1984', featuring Big Brother and a society under constant surveillance?",
    choices: {
      A: 'Aldous Huxley',
      B: 'George Orwell',
      C: 'Ernest Hemingway',
      D: 'F. Scott Fitzgerald',
    },
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Although many people think of Sydney or Melbourne, which city is actually the capital of Australia and home to its Parliament House?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Sydney',
      B: 'Melbourne',
      C: 'Canberra',
      D: 'Brisbane',
    },
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which musical instrument, found in classical orchestras and popular music alike, features black and white keys and produces sound by hammers striking strings?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Piano',
      B: 'Violin',
      C: 'Trumpet',
      D: 'Drums',
    },
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question:
      "In computer terminology, what does the acronym 'CPU' stand for, referring to the part of the machine that processes instructions and performs calculations?",
    choices: {
      A: 'Central Processing Unit',
      B: 'Control Peripheral Unit',
      C: 'Compute Performance Utility',
      D: 'Central Peripheral User',
    },
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which actor appeared in both the shows 'Lost' and 'The Office', playing significant roles in each, but not in 'Breaking Bad'?",
    choices: {
      A: 'Bryan Cranston',
      B: 'Rainn Wilson',
      C: 'Matthew Fox',
      D: 'Michael Emerson',
    },
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question:
      "Located in Siberia, which lake is considered the world's deepest and holds about 20% of Earth’s unfrozen fresh water?",
    choices: {
      A: 'Lake Baikal',
      B: 'Lake Tanganyika',
      C: 'Caspian Sea',
      D: 'Lake Superior',
    },
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who is the only chess player to have won the World Chess Championship in three formats: knockout, tournament, and match play?',
    choices: {
      A: 'Garry Kasparov',
      B: 'Magnus Carlsen',
      C: 'Viswanathan Anand',
      D: 'Bobby Fischer',
    },
    answer: 'C',
  },
]
